Let's get this over with. so I can
get back to Danny's office
and apologise. It's gonna be fine.
This programme contains some strong
language and scenes of a sexual nature.
Thank you for coming.
What do you want?
Sorry.
Vadim? What are you doing here?
A surface of revolution
is a surface...
defined by...
z equals capital H of r.
where r. z and theta are...?
Anyone?
Cylindrical polar coordinates.
Thank you. Saara.
I'm glad someone's listening.
OK. so. our...
cylindrical polar coordinates...
Of increased anti-Russian feeling.
fanned by inflammatory statements...
Vadim!
By British politicians.
The Russian Government has concluded
that this presents
a real threat to
the safety of our citizens in the UK
and. therefore. they should all
return to Russia immediately.
So that's breaking news. Russian
TV say all Russian citizens
in the UK must make
immediate arrangements
to return home.
by presidential executive order.
Shit.
I'm seeing red lights.
Tahmid. What's going on?
Tahmid. what's...?
We're down. We're down.
What did you do?
Er. nothing. We're just logging on.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm Max. Hi.
We're not shaking hands at the moment.
Of course. Sorry.
Welcome to GCHQ.
Partial shutdown.
As far as we can tell. about 55%...
Chrissie. have you met Max?
He's our head of malware.
Hi. Pleased to meet you.
At 9.07 this morning... VIDEO STOPS.
You speak good English. I think.
Hello. Roman Nikitin.
Er...
Roman Nikitin. Nikitin.
Thank you for coming.
What do you want?
Sorry.
Vadim? What are you doing here?
I don't have very long.
There is something you haven't found
yet. something hidden.
What? You need to search for it.
Where? What are we searching for?
In the malware.
It's hidden in the malware.
You need to find it before it activates.
But I already found it.
It was due to activate on the Monday
after the attack but we stopped it.
No. no. no. not that.
Something else. Something new.
What? There's nothing else -
we've checked.
Listen. It's really dangerous.
It could cause a war.
You can stop it.
Look in the malware.
It's hidden in the malware.
Vadim. wait.
You haven't told me anything.
You have to give me more to go on.
I'm really glad it's you. Saara.
Please. Please don't tell my name.
not to anyone.
I put my life in your hands now. OK?
If they find out I told you this.
they will kill me.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media